pro-medics.com 2011-10-16

# Privacy policy

We are firmly committed to your privacy and guarantee that none of the information provided by our customers will be given to third parties. With the "Order Form" we collect contact information such as your email address and financial information such as your credit card number. This information is only used to fulfill our customers orders.

Financial information is collected and used solely for the billing of products and for services offered by our website.  
During a purchase we collect your address, phone numbers, email address and credit card details, which is used solely for shipping and contact purposes.

An order history of your purchases is also maintained, enabling tracking of deliveries and reviewing your past purchases. Based on your order history we may create special offers or purchase rewards.

We collect general information regarding the number of 'hits' to our website and monitor traffic patterns that help us build a more user-friendly site. We do not track individual user pathways through the site!

Our site uses 'cookies' - small pieces of code sent to your web browser by a web server. They do not harm your computer in any way. These small text files can be found inside your 'Temporary Internet Files' folder under Windows. Cookies keep track of the items in your Shopping Cart and act as temporary place markers when you move around the site. If set your Security Settings in Internet Explorer to 'high' cookies are disabled. In order to use this site you need to set the security level for the Internet to Medium (under Tools/Internet Options). This provides "Safe browsing but still functional." Alternatively you can add this site to your list of trusted sites.

If you have any concerns regarding our site, please contact us and we`ll be glad to discuss any issues with you.

We NEVER exchange, sell or otherwise give away your email address to any other companies. Your email address is used solely by you, for purposes of logging into your account. Your email address is used solely as a means for contacting your about your orders and the newsletter.

In order to complete your order we have to disclose some of your information to service suppliers, including EMS and USPS.

## Consent

By using our website you give us permission to use your personal information for orders, services and updates only, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns, please contact us and we'll gladly discuss it with you.

## Security

When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card or debit card information is encrypted using SSL encryption technology, before being sent over the Internet. We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database separately from our website database. It is not connected to the Internet, as the protection against hackers.

## Unsolicited Email (SPAM)

Your privacy is very important to us and you can rest assured that we do not sell or distribute our customer list to any third parties. However, please be aware that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes "harvest" your email address directly from your computer or another person's address book, perhaps using programs that automatically scan web pages and email traffic in order to obtain email addresses.

If you receive an unsolicited email that you believe is connected with us in any way, please forward it (as an attachment) to service@PrimaryPills and we will investigate promptly.  
Children

We do not allow underage purchases. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Links may lead to other online stores operated and maintained by separate companies. We cannot be responsible for linked websites (including those participating in our Affiliates Program). We provide these links to our visitors solely for convenience and valuable information. Privacy policies of such sites may differ from our policy and you are advised to review individual privacy statements on any site you visit.
